<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<InfoWarnings>
  <Info>Begin full analysis with NDepend v2019.2.6</Info>
  <Warning>Last day of evaluation.
You can ask for evaluation extension if required from the menu Help then License Information.</Warning>
  <Info>Compare with analysis result obtained on 2019 July - 26 Friday 14:27  (which is the analysis result with date closest to 30 days ago)</Info>
  <Info>.NET Assembly resolved from the Visual Studio solution file {C:\Users\320053936\source\repos\PractiseApp\PractiseApp.sln}
   C:\Users\320053936\source\repos\PractiseApp\PractiseApp\bin\Debug\PractiseApp.exe</Info>
  <Info>.NET Assembly filtered out from the Visual Studio solution file {C:\Users\320053936\source\repos\PractiseApp\PractiseApp.sln}
   UnitTestProject1</Info>
  <Info>Serial mode</Info>
  <Info>.NET Assemblies loaded from {C:\WINDOWS\Microsoft.NET\Framework\v4.0.30319} 
   System.Configuration.dll   v4.0.0.0
   System.dll   v4.0.0.0
   System.Xml.Linq.dll   v4.0.0.0
   mscorlib.dll   v4.0.0.0</Info>
  <Info>8 source files parsed ; all source files found ; all source files in-sync with PDB</Info>
  <Info>0 code rule has been extracted from code.</Info>
  <Info>No dependency cycle detected in assemblies referencement graph.</Info>
  <Info>Do merge code generated by compiler into application code.</Info>
  <Info>Analyse dependencies of your application.</Info>
  <Info>No SuppressMessageAttribute found in the analyzed code base. Since NDepend v2018.2 SuppressMessageAttribute can be used to suppress NDepend issues. Don't forget to set in your projects the compilation symbol CODE_ANALYSIS to use this attribute to suppress NDepend issues.</Info>
  <Info>Execute queries and rules.</Info>
  <Warning>2 quality gates warn:
  - 'New Debt since Baseline' value 0.24 man-days greater than warn threshold 0 man-days
  - 'New Annual Interest since Baseline' value 1.34 man-days greater than warn threshold 0 man-days</Warning>
  <Error>3 quality gates fail:
  - 'New Blocker / Critical / High Issues' value 13 issues greater than fail threshold 0 issues
  - 'Critical Rules Violated' value 1 rules greater than fail threshold 0 rules
  - 'Debt Rating per Namespace' value 1 namespaces greater than fail threshold 0 namespaces</Error>
  <Info>NDepend analysis done. Duration: 00:38</Info>
  <Info>Building the report (standard).</Info>
</InfoWarnings>